# **Dustin Delatore**

dustin@delatore.me (603) 767-0614 http://whosdustin.com

Over 10 years of web design and 6 years front-end development experience. All of my attention was focused on creating the best user experience possible. Highly motivated, hard working and an ambitious leader prepared for any challenges that confront me.

Twitter whos\_dustin Github whosdustin

#### **SKILLS**

FRONT-END
HTML5, CSS3, Sass/Less, Javascript, jQuery, Responsive Development,
Markdown, Git

UI DESIGN
Photoshop, Illustrator, Iconography, Interface Design

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Bisk Education**

Front-end/Mobile Developer May 2014 - Present

Worked primarily on the Bisk Learning Management System (LMS). Supported in converting the LMS from a fixed width site to a fully responsive application. Optimized the entire front-end of the LMS with thorough research and documentation of development standards. I modified the platform from a feature/page specific stylesheet to a scalable and modular architecture css using Grunt and Sass. Also, part of the first mobile development team to create Bisk's first mobile application.

- Built a front-end development standards documentation
- Successfully converted an application to responsive design
- Optimized CSS for scalabilty and performance on page load
- Kicked off Bisk's first mobile application team
- Built a mobile app for iOS and Android using Appcelerator's Titanium platform

# **LilyPad Solutions**

Lead Designer/Front-end Developer Jul 2011 - May 2014

Joined a group of individuals to design their first app and website. Helped assist the one developer build the iOS app in Titanium Studio on their Javascript platform. Company pivoted to another product; received funding and hired me full-time.

- LilyPad App An iPad app to broadcast presentations across multiple devices and encourage user engagement. Designed the entire app which was already set on top of a pre-existing framework.
- LilyPad App Website Designed from wireframe and all of the images on the site (excluding the frog). Teamed up with an illustrator to help create the companies mascot.

- LilyPad Sales Mobile App An outside sales team's motivational activity driven tool. Worked on branding and style guides for application. Wireframed and prototyped early designs prior to launch. Complete design of entire application and iconography for release on iOS. Converted designs and rebuilt on Android following release of iOS.
- LilyPad Sales Web App Teamed up with the developer to release a dashboard application for managers LilyPad Sales Website Bootstrap built and designed landing pages along with main company site.

#### Actsoft

Designer/Front-end Developer Jan 2009 - Feb 2013

Dealt with everything web related in a small in-house marketing team at Actsoft. Took on several roles within the small team such as tackling a large amount of the marketing needs from designing and building websites, email marketing campaigns, to helping create a social presence.

- Actsoft's Main Site Built on Wordpress. The entire team worked on this project from the beginning stages of site map creation to final site launch. Was responsible for the user experience and layout of the project. Assisted in implementing the companies first ever Wordpress website and performance optimization.
- Advanced Wireless Forms Cross platform forms app. Designed and built the static marketing website. Dashtrac - Plug & Play vehicle tracking device (Even named product).
   Designed and built the marketing website.

### **VOLUNTEERING**

# **University of Tampa**

Teacher's Assistant Feb 2008 - May 2008

Supervised and taught several web design and development classes; while finishing my senior year at UT.

### **EDUCATION**

# **University of Tampa**

Aug 2005 - May 2008 Bachelor - Electronic Media Arts and Technology GPA: 3.3